{"test_questions": [[{"question": "FAD is reduced to FADH2 during", "opta": "electron transport phosphorylation", "optb": "lactate fermentation", "optc": "Krebs cycle", "optd": "glycolysis", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "During glycolysis, electrons removed from glucose are passed to", "opta": "FAD", "optb": "NAD+", "optc": "acetyl CoA", "optd": "pyruvic acid", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A biological redox reaction always involves", "opta": "an oxidizing agent", "optb": "a gain of electrons", "optc": "a reducing agent", "optd": "all of these", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Coenzyme Q is involved in electron transport as", "opta": "directly to O2", "optb": "a water-soluble electron donor", "optc": "covalently attached cytochrome cofactor", "optd": "a lipid-soluble electron carrier", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The carbon dioxide is primary a product of", "opta": "Krebs cycle", "optb": "glycolysis", "optc": "electron transport phosphorylation.", "optd": "lactate fermentation.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a feature of oxidative phosphorylation?", "opta": "Direct transfer of phosphate from a substrate molecule to ADP", "optb": "An electrochemical gradient across the inner mitochondrial membrane", "optc": "A membrane bound ATP synthase", "optd": "A protonmotive force", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a significant biological oxidizing agent?", "opta": "FAD", "optb": "Fe3+", "optc": "O2", "optd": "NAD+", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many CO2 molecules are exhaled for each O2 molecule utilized in cellular respiration?", "opta": "1", "optb": "3", "optc": "6", "optd": "12", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What happens after glycolysis when oxygen is available as an electron acceptor?", "opta": "Pyruvate is formed", "optb": "NADH is produced", "optc": "Fermentation", "optd": "Oxidative phosphorylation", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Lactic acid is produced by human muscles during strenuous exercise because of lack of", "opta": "oxygen", "optb": "NAD+", "optc": "glucose", "optd": "ADP and Pi", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is correct sequence of processes in the oxidation of glucose?", "opta": "Krebs cycle - glycolysis - electron transport", "optb": "Glycolysis - Krebs cycle - eletron transport", "optc": "Electron transport - Krebs cycle - glycolysis", "optd": "Krebs cycle - electron transport - glycolysis", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In electron transport, electrons ultimately pass to", "opta": "ADP", "optb": "cytochrome b", "optc": "oxygen", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The complete oxidation of glucose yields usable energy in the form of", "opta": "FADH2", "optb": "coenzyme A", "optc": "ATP", "optd": "pyruvic acid", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "During electron transport, protons are pumped out of the mitochondrion at each of the major sites except for", "opta": "complex I", "optb": "complex II", "optc": "complex III", "optd": "complex IV", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The aerobic breakdown of glucose known as respiration involves", "opta": "electron transport phosphorylation", "optb": "glycolysis", "optc": "Krebs Cycle", "optd": "all of  the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In aerobic respiration, the compound that enters a mitochondrion is", "opta": "acetyl CoA", "optb": "pyruvate", "optc": "phosphoglyceraldehyde", "optd": "oxaloacetate", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}